rythercamera.com 2011-12-05

# RytherCamera.com Digital Cameras, Camcorders and Photography Accessories

**Privacy Statement**  
RytherCamera.com has created this privacy statement in order to establish our firm promise and commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website RytherCamera.com. Please review the lists and details below.

  * We DO NOT sell/share/rent any of your personal information with any third party.
  * We use it ONLY for processing and fulfilling your order.
  * We will NOT add your personal information to any mailing lists.

RytherCamera.com WILL

  * Treat your privacy very seriously and will adhere to this Privacy Policy.
  * Promote this Privacy Policy internally so all employees abide by it. 
  * Keep this Privacy Policy accurate and up to date.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information and purchase products. We collect customer contact information such as their email address and credit card information such as their credit card numbers. Contact information from the order form is used to send and verify orders to our customers. The customer's contact information and e-mail address is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Credit card information that is collected is used solely for billing purposes ONLY.

You can easily subscribe or unsubscribe for our money saving newsletter from your [account login.](http://www.rythercamera.com/catalog/account.php) Please login to your account and scroll down to "E-Mail Notifications", and click on "Subscribe or unsubscribe from newsletters".

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We offer a Secure Socket Layer server on our ordering pages by which you will send your ordering information so the data will be sent and is able to be viewed ONLY by  authorized persons at RytherCamera.com.  
Information collected is protected by the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, which prevents any sensitive information from being compromised.

To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your Web browser's status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of most browsers such as Internet Explorer and Firefox.  Also, all browsers display an "s" after the "http" (https://…) in the Web site address to indicate that you're in a secure environment.

At RytherCamera.com, we are devoted to protecting your privacy online. Your Private Information will never be disclosed to anyone and will be used for business purposes only. All orders are placed through a secure online server. We Use VeriSign, a trusted third party eCommerce Security Company to assure your security-Only authorized persons have access to your information.

We also protect your purchase by preventing the shipments to a fraudulent address. All billing addresses are verified electronically and all alternate shipping addresses are verified manually. Any customer shipping to an address that differs from the billing address must put this alternate address on file with their credit card company. We then call the credit card issuer to verify that the customer has indeed put the information on file. If your uncomfortable ordering online you can always order by telephone, toll free 1-877-644-7593.

**Credit Card Fraud Warranty**

We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at our online store. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank generally cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to help identify you when you visit our store and to customize your experience. The cookie contains a randomly assigned user identification number, the country where you are located, and we may track where you came from, and how you browse our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies. We do not disclose your personal account information or any information about your purchases to anyone.  
When you leave our site, we are no longer responsible for protecting your privacy. We suggest you review the policies of the new site. These other sites may use their own "cookies", collect data or solicit personal information from you. Please be advised RytherCamera.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and guidelines on these sites.

**Protection of Children**

We do not direct our website to children, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). When placing an order on the RytherCamera.com website, you are affirming that you are an adult. Users under the age of thirteen must ask a parent or guardian for assistance while placing an order online.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our website. For additional questions please contact us at: victor@RytherCamera.com

Shipping charges do not include handling, processing & insurance charges which may be additional. If you placed an order online choosing the free shipping option or any other shipping option, on an item which may or may not qualify, you will be contacted by our support department informing you of any additional charges. Please contact our customer service department(877-644-7593) if you are unsure if the item you are purchasing qualifies. 

Our free shipping promotion does not qualify on orders containing more than one unit. You may be charged a shipping fee per each additional item. For exact shipping costs please contact our sales department at 877-644-7593.
